(Sheldon:)You ask anyone, that's a hot date.
(Amy:)Tempting choices, but I have
something special planned for tonight.
(Sheldon:)What can be more special than having
an adequate amount of time...
(Sheldon:)...to cross the street on your way
to buy a tiny Lego lndiana Jones?
(Amy:)With our friends moving forward
in relationships...
...l have decided
we should make progress in ours.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord.
(Sheldon:)Two years ago,
we didn't even know each other...
(Sheldon:)...and now I'm in your apartment
after dark.
(Sheldon:)How much faster can this thing go?
(Amy:)Had a feeling you'd be reluctant...
(Amy:)...which is why I'm going to dip
into my bag of tricks.
Oh, heh, you brain-monkeys kill me.
Dip away.
l have devised an experiment that
l believe will increase your feelings...
- ...for me in an accelerated time-frame.
- Well, how do you propose to do that?
Uh, I hope you're not thinking about
some sort of LSD thought-control.
(Sheldon:)There's only one mind-expanding drug
that this man enjoys.
(Sheldon:)And that's called school.